<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<config>
	<ticker>
		<lang id="en-US">The demo will end on the 25th of February --- Thank you for playing the demo &amp; don’t forget to reserve BFBC2 limited edition: includes 6 unlocks, at no extra charge! *Limited supplies with participating retailers only. Follow us on Twitter @officialBFBC2 and BATTLEFIELD.COM for the latest news. --- </lang>
		<lang id="fr-FR">The demo will end on the 25th of February --- Merci d’avoir participé à la démo et pensez à réserver l’Edition Limitée de BFBC2 qui contient 6 unlocks sans coût additionnel ! Attention – le seul et unique moyen d’obtenir cette édition est de réserver le jeu ! Soyez toujours les premiers informés et rejoignez nous sur Facebook : www.facebook.com/Battlefield . --- </lang>
		<lang id="de-DE">The demo will end on the 25th of February --- Vielen Dank, dass du die Demo spielst! Sichere dir jetzt die Limited Edition von BFBC2, um dir von Anfang an einen Vorteil auf dem Schlachtfeld zu verschaffen. Die Limited Edition gewährt dir Zugang zu verschiedenen Fahrzeugkampf-Freischaltungen, sowie zu zwei Waffen aus Battlefield 1943. Alle Infos auf BATTLEFIELD.DE --- </lang>
		<lang id="es-ES">The demo will end on the 25th of February --- Gracias por participar en la demo. No olvides reservar tu Edición Limitada de BFBC2: incluye 6 desbloqueos, sin coste adicional. La Edición Limitada la puedes conseguir en EA Store o en los puntos de venta participantes. Siguenos en Facebook (www.facebook.com/battlefield.es) o en WWW.BATTLEFIELD.ES para recibir las últimas noticias. --- </lang>
		<lang id="it-IT">The demo will end on the 25th of February --- Grazie per aver giocato il demo &amp; non dimenticare di prenotare la  limited edition di BFBC2: include 6 bonus sbloccabili, senza sovrapprezzo! *Quantità limitate con i negozi aderenti. Seguici su Twitter @officialBFBC2 e su BATTLEFIED.COM per le ultime news. --- </lang>
		<lang id="pl-PL">The demo will end on the 25th of February --- Dziękujemy za grę w demo Battlefield Bad Company 2. Nie zapomnij zarezerwować swojego egzemplarza Edycji Limitowanej, który zawiera 6 ulepszeń bez dodatkowych kosztów. Ilośc egzemplarzy Edycji Limitowanej ograniczona. Śledź najświeższe wiadomości na Twitterze @officialBFBC2 oraz na BATTLEFIELD.COM --- </lang>
		<lang id="jp-JP">The demo will end on the 25th of February --- Thank you for playing the demo &amp; don’t forget to reserve BFBC2!  Follow us on Twitter @officialBFBC2 and BATTLEFIELD.COM for the latest news. --- </lang>
	</ticker>
</config>